( sewing machine clicking )
( screaming )
( sobbing )
What 's wrong with my eye , Mama ?
Mama : The doctor says it 's lazy .
But ...
we 're going to make you look perfect .
It itches .
Do you want make friends ?
Then keep it covered .
Are you a pirate ?
( children muttering )
( school bell rings )
Man : ¶ Happy Birthday to you . ¶
I 've always said ,
" If you can 't find a friend ,
make one . "
Happy birthday , sweetheart .
( Mama sighs )
Now it 's ruined .
Her name is Suzie .
Suzie was the first doll I ever made .
She was my best friend .
And now she 'll be yours .
No , no , no , you can 't take her out .
She 's special .
What do you think of my pirate patch ?
I bet you 're wondering what I 'm making .
Okay , I 'll tell you . ( giggles )
I saw someone today .
A boy .
You know how when you meet someone ...
and you think you like them ,
but then the more you talk to them
you see parts you don 't like .
Like that guy on the bench .
And sometimes ...
you don 't end up liking any parts at all .
But ...
the boy I saw today is different .
I like every part of him .
Especially his hands .
They 're beautiful .
Don 't be mad .
You 've been my friend my whole life .
And you see me , you always have , but ...
I need a real friend .
Someone I can hold .
I 'm going to give you some cardboard shades
you can wear over your regular glasses
until the dilation wears off .
Will my contacts be ready by Friday ?
Doctor : Should be .
You look awfully excited .
I have a date .
You 're sure my eye won 't cross with the contacts ?
Positive .
The contacts will pull your good eye forward
just like your regular glasses .
Your lazy eye just needs a little help .
I need all the help I can get .
This boy is perfect .
¶ If I saw you ¶
¶ Now ¶
¶ Could I look in your ¶
¶ Eyes ? ¶
¶ Do you think of me ¶
¶ Like I dream of you ? ¶
¶ Do you wish you were here ¶
¶ Like I wish I ... ¶
Oh , slick shades .
What the hell is a scupel ?
- Scalpel ? - Oh !
Your dog 's going to be fine , ma 'am .
( sighs ) Scalpel !
Thanks for the heads up , doll .
Scupel .
Man : Wait ! Hold ' em up !
Moy , I need a big scupel for German Shepard surgery tomorrow .
No forget it . Prep it up for me .
Hey , May , hold up .
I want to ask you something .
What are you going to be for Halloween ?
I 've just been wracking my brains , you know ,
trying to come up with something original .
Do you got any ideas ?
You have a beautiful neck .
Thank you .
You should call me one of these nights .
You know , we 'll hang out and ...
eat some melons or something .
Okay .
( elevator dings )
¶ Come on , come on back to me right now ¶
¶ Come on , come on , come on ¶
¶ Do you love me now ? ¶
¶ Did you love me before ? ¶
When I left for vacation ,
my dog had four legs .
Okay ?
Then I came back ...
now she only has three .
You know , I looked everywhere .
I can 't find her leg .
What do I do ?
May ?
May , would you help this gentleman ?
You got to help me here , May .
I got a serious situation here , okay ?
I got a dog , it 's missing a leg , okay ?
I 'm throwing it a stick and nothing .
Nothing happens .
Hello ?
Polly : Jesus , what are you doing ?
Relaxing .
Doesn 't it hurt ?
No .
Ow !
You crazy bitch !
Why did you do that ? !
Actually ...
I kind of liked it .
Do me again .
( giggles )
( flesh tearing )
( gasping )
Man : It was in the rose bushes .
You can 't just ...
sew it back on ...
can you ?
I could .
Hello .
You can use me ...
I mean , mine .
Thank you .
- What 's your name ? - May .
Nice to meet you . I 'm Adam .
You want to smoke
a smoke with me ?
You got to puff .
So , do you make your own clothes ?
Yes .
That 's cool .
Thank you , Adam .
You 're welcome , May .
I love your hands .
I think they 're beautiful .
I used to be a hand model .
- I could see you doing that . - I 'm kidding , May .
( giggles )
Whoa !
( dryer buzzes )
Oh !
Well ...
Race cars .
What 's that ?
Oh , yeah .
My , uh ...
girlfriend bought me these .
Anyway .
You know , I meant , my ex-girlfriend ...
bought them for me .
Practice .
I 'll see you around , May .
( dryer buzzes )
" Hey , see you around , right ? "
I 'm so sorry that ...
I tripped in front of you
at the coffee shop .
Maybe we could ...
we could do something .
( giggles )
" See you around . "
" See you around , right ? "
Hello , happy !
Dr. Zarkizein needs you to do a fecosam
on the miscitta .
Does that make any sense to you ?
Fecal exam on Miss Kitty . No problem .
Oh , excuse me .
Hey !
What 's up , May ?
I was just about to ...
about to have lunch . Wow , you look great !
You hungry ?
I will cut .
And you pick .
Good choice .
So what do you do , May ?
I work at the animal hospital .
And I sew .
Okay . Animal hospital .
Some people think it 's kind of gross .
I love gross .
- Really ? - Mm-hmm .
Disgust me , please .
Okay .
A couple of weeks ago , this old man comes in
and says his dog is dying .
And he begs us to save it .
A 90-pound black Lab named Seymour .
We take him in and run some tests
and we find that he has a twisted bowel .
And he needs to be operated on immediately .
So , we shave Seymour 's tummy ,
we cut him open
and we take out a piece of intestine about ,
about the size of a hot-dog .
Everything went smooth ,
but ...
when we went to sew Seymour back up ,
we realized we were out of the heavy sutures
that you 're supposed to use for large dogs .
So the doctor decided if we tripled up
on cat sutures that should do the trick .
Well ,
a few days go by
and the old man calls up
hysterical .
The cat sutures had burst when he was at work .
And by the time he got home ,
Seymour was sprawled out on the back porch
with his guts spread all over the concrete .
And the fence was soaked in blood
all the way around the yard .
It was a mess .
I had to sew that one back up .
So , I guess your job takes lots of guts .
Lots .
Why are those kids touching everything like that ?
Adam : They 're blind kids .
They 're from the day care center around the block .
Dang , I got to go .
There 's an Argenta playing at the Beverly in 15 minutes .
I took the afternoon off . They 're showing " Trauma . "
- Is that a movie ? - You 've never seen " Trauma " ?
Don 't go .
What ?
Nothing .
I should probably get back to work , anyway .
Thank you for the sandwich ...
and the cigarette .
I got to see this movie ,
but maybe I can see you again sometime .
How about tonight ?
I got this thing tonight , but ...
- maybe after . - Great !
All right . I look forward to it , May .
You want to take it with you ?
Thanks for the advice , doll .
So ...
what were you doing to me that day at the coffee shop ?
I 'm so embarrassed .
Why ?
I 've never had a boyfriend before .
Do you like me , Adam ?
Sure , I do .
You don 't think I 'm weird ?
I do think you 're weird .
- I knew that . - I like weird .
I like weird a lot .
You are perfect , aren 't you ?
Nobody 's perfect .
You 're perfect .
You want to see my room ?
Does this stuff freak you out ?
Nothing freaks me out .
That 's right , it wouldn 't , would it ?
You 're on to me .
I 'm a psycho .
Got you .
It 's pretty cool , huh ?
Whoa ! Jesus Christ !
Who taught you how to kiss ?
Suzie .
Who taught you how to kiss ? !
( glass breaks )
Ah !
( crackling )
( cat meows )
What 's the haps , doll ?
What happened to your hand ?
Scupel .
( giggles )
You 're funny .
You want to watch me file ?
Hey .
We got the whole place to ourselves .
Let 's dance .
( music plays )
( humming )
( dogs barking )
( giggling )
Listen , they 're serenading us .
We have to dance now .
Oh .
Please , please , please .
Please .
So , are you going to dance with me or what ?
- Do you like pussy ? - What ? !
Cats ?
Do you like pussycats ?
Jeez , you 're a nasty little thing , aren 't you ?
Do you like Lupe ?
My landlady 's a real bitch .
I have to get rid of her .
Your landlady ?
No , dummy , the cat .
You 're her only hope .
Oh , come on .
Lupe will keep you company when you 're all alone .
Besides ,
she 'll remind you of me .
- Okay . - Wonderful !
Oh , look at the time .
I have to go .
It 's girls ' night out tonight .
You want to come ?
I know .
You need your beauty rest .
Not much of it , though .
Recording : Please leave a message after the scream .
( screaming )
Hello , Adam , this is May .
I was just wondering if you would like to be together again ...
( glass cracking )
( sighs )
Get together again sometime .
I had such a good time last night .
742-5663 . That 's my number .
Call me .
Anytime .
I look forward to seeing you again .
¶ Yes ¶
¶ What is it , my love ? ¶
¶ He said , " It 's nothing ¶
¶ Nothing really ¶
¶ Just wanted to hear ¶
¶ Your cute voice ¶
¶ To know you are near " ¶
¶ And he calls me " kitten " ¶
¶ Kitten ¶
¶ When it 's quiet and ... ¶
Whoa ! Jesus Christ !
May , you scared the hell out of me !
What are you doing out here ?
Nothing .
How long have you been standing out here ?
Since about 2 : 00 .
You haven 't really been standing out here for two hours , have you ?
What do you think ?
Look , I got your message .
I 'm sorry I haven 't called you back .
I 've been really busy with this movie .
You made a movie ?
In college before I dropped out . I just finished putting it together .
Can I see it ?
I 'll make you macaroni and cheese .
Go to a movie , huh ?
Sounds like a date .
I dig your place .
It 's really ...
neat .
Is this Gatorade ?
Cool .
You 'll never believe what I had to do at work today .
You ready ?
Roll ' em .
¶ My baby does the Hanky Panky ¶
¶ Hey , my baby does the Hanky Panky ¶
¶ I saw her walking on down the line ¶
¶ You know I saw her for the very first time ¶
¶ A pretty little girl standing all alone ¶
¶ Hey , pretty baby , can I take you home ? ¶
¶ I never saw her , never ever saw her ¶
¶ My baby does the Hanky Panky ¶
¶ Yeah , my baby does the Hanky Panky ¶
¶ Let s go ! ¶
( guitar solo )
Adam : So ?
What did you think ?
It was sweet .
It was sweet ?
I don 't think she could have gotten
his whole finger in one bite , though .
That part was kind of far-fetched .
¶ Oh ¶
¶ Last flight ¶
¶ Get lost in the moss ¶
¶ Oh , oh ¶
¶ Fall in the neon mine ¶
¶ Push me down ¶
Okay , okay , breathe
¶ Still rolling in the stones ¶
¶ Run to the log that s rotten ¶
¶ Oh , oh ¶
¶ Your soft belly bossing lows ¶
¶ Push me down ¶
Oh , God damn it !
What the fuck is that ?
- Oh , fuck , I 'm bleeding . - I know .
May , what are you doing ?
Please . I need a towel .
I think ... I think I 'm gonna go .
What ?
I 'll see you around .
But it 's just like your movie .
May , this is weird .
You like weird .
Not that weird .
( distant whispering )
( glass cracking )
( glass crashes )
May : I told you to face the goddamn wall !
Oops ! It fall down .
Moy , you help me .
Doctor , this delivery guy is insisting
that you sign for this .
I 'm in surgery , Polly , please !
Yeah , yeah , that 's good . Kitty live now .
- Man : What are you doing ? - Adam : What ?
Take it outside , man .
So , what 's up , bro ' ? What do you think ?
Adam : Fuck , she 's pretty .
I don 't think she 's playing with a full deck .
- That 's not what you wanted . - True .
At least you know she 's not out of her mind .
You know what , we 're not talking about May anymore .
I 've successfully escaped that lunatic .
Woman : Who 's May ?
Man : Some weird chick Adam just dumped .
How 's your lip ?
Adam : Stow it , all right ? Would you , please ?
Woman : I see . May I ?
Man : So what if she likes your hands ?
Just keep them away from her face .
Adam : You 're a prick , you know that ?
- Yeah , do some more pushups . - Man : Fuck you .
( phone beeps ) What 's up , doll ?
This is Polly .
I 'm just sitting here in my nightie .
I wanted to know how my little puss-puss was .
Come on over if you get this , okay ?
What 's giving you the sads , doll ?
Oh .
No frumpy faces allowed in this place .
¶ When it 's quiet under ¶
¶ I say , yes , yes , yes ¶
¶ What is it , my heart ? ¶
¶ He says nothing ¶
¶ Not really ¶
¶ It 's just I miss you so ¶
¶ You know how . ¶
I wanted to kiss you since I first saw you .
Is this what was bugging you ?
I wasn 't bugged .
Just angry at someone .
Not me , I hope .
No , not you .
Do you feel weird doing this ?
I am weird .
I love weird .
Are you serious ?
Yeah .
About me ?
Dead .
¶ He calls me kitten ¶
¶ Kitten ¶
¶ In the middle of the night ¶
¶ I say yes , yes , yes ¶
¶ What is it , my life ? ¶
¶ He says , " Nothing , not really , ¶
¶ For the angels I wish ¶
¶ For the angels that took you ¶
¶ The angels I wish . ¶
Can you help us with something ?
I saw some kids playing in the park
and I was wondering if I could volunteer
to help watch them .
What kind of kids were they ? Retarded , deaf , crippled , dumb ?
They were blind .
So you want to work at the day care center ?
Would it be the same kids ?
What 's the difference ? You only like a certain type of blind kids ?
( children singing )
May Kennedy ? Lucille .
Let 's introduce you to the kids .
Do you think I could meet her first ?
Lucille : Who , Petey ? We can try .
She usually likes being left alone .
Nobody likes to be alone .
Hey , Petey , I got someone here who wants to meet you .
Go away , sniggel-head .
You are so mean to me , Petey .
Good luck .
What are you making , Petey ?
Ashtray .
You smoke ?
No .
Then who are you making the ash tray for , Petey ?
You smoke .
Yes , I do .
Then you can have it when I 'm done .
How you doing , May ?
Great , actually .
Making new friends .
Right and left .
Lovely .
Lupe ,
this is Adam .
It 's cute .
How are you doing ?
Aw , man , this thing is broke .
I 'm gonna have to go down to the Fluff and Fold .
Call me sometime ?
Yeah , sure . I 'll see you around , May .
( machine starts )
May !
What 's up ?
Woman : Who is it , Polly ?
Who is that ?
An opportunity I just couldn 't pass up .
Oh .
You want to join us ?
Well , then can we do something tomorrow , May ?
I got to hit this .
I don 't understand .
You 're jealous !
- What 's going on out there ? - Shut up , hooker !
Oh , May , look .
I can kick her out if you really want me to .
You know you 're my main mama .
( glass cracking )
( sobbing )
( coughs )
Come here , Lup . Come here .
Come on .
Come on , girl , it 's been a really rough couple of days .
( hisses )
( clay shatters )
( glass cracks )
Shut up !
( cracking stops )
Thank you .
( phone beeping )
Adam : Hello ?
- Is Adam there ? - Hey , what 's up ?
Not much .
How did you know it was me ?
Hello ?
Who is this ?
May , silly .
( glass cracking )
What are you doing tonight ?
Hello ?
Why ?
( cracking intensifies )
I was just thinking we could get together
and do something .
I have plans .
- ( glass breaks ) - Oh .
Quiet !
Hello ? Who are you talking to ?
May : What about tomorrow night ?
Adam : Maybe .
Maybe ?
Okay , what time ? I 'll wait .
Don 't do that .
No , no , no . It 's okay . I 'll wait .
I got to go , May .
( giggles )
Okay . Well , I 'll talk to you tomorrow then .
Goodbye , May .
( glass rattles )
I hate you .
May : Who can tell me what this is ?
Girl : We don 't know , May , what is it ?
Petey , come here and see if you can figure it out .
I don 't know .
Come on , Petey , you can try harder than that .
All right , I 'll tell you what it is .
Girl : What , what is it ?
This is my best friend .
My best friend .
And I didn 't even realize it until just last night .
It 's just a box .
- Her friend must be inside . - That 's very good , Deirdre .
Petey : Take it out .
I can 't .
- Why not ? - I just can 't .
Come on , May , let it out . We want to meet your friend .
No , I ...
I can 't . She 's special . She doesn 't come out .
She always stays in . She 's very fragile .
Petey .
Stop it !
- She 's out ! - No !
- The floor ! - Glass !
Don 't !
Glass ! Ow !
( screaming )
( phone ringing )
May 's voice : This is May Kennedy .
Please leave your numbers .
( phone beeps )
Polly : Hello . Where are you , doll ?
I think Dr. Zarkizein is upset .
Either that or he has a kidney infection .
I 'm not sure .
Either way , you need to get your cute butt in here .
You 've missed two days in a row .
Are you all right ?
I miss you . Kisses .
Call me , okay ?
Ah .
Oh , Lupe .
I 'll miss petting your pretty fur .
Are you okay ?
So many pretty parts and no pretty holes .
No shit . What 's your name ?
It doesn 't matter .
Hey , you want to go get some Jujubes with me ?
What 's the point ?
I 'm just trying to be friendly .
Sorry .
Hmm ...
Shit , man , I can live off of these .
It 's getting hella hot .
You mind if I take off my shirt ?
- Do what you want . - All right .
I love your tattoo .
Thanks .
Ah .
Fuck ! I 'm still burning up .
Do you have any ice cubes I can rub on my nipples ?
May : Freeze !
That 's the idea .
Stop !
What the fuck is that ?
- A friend . - Whoa .
This is some sick shit .
So ...
are we best friends now that you 've seen what 's inside my freezer ?
You fucking freak .
I 'm not going to be your friend .
( sobbing )
( screaming )
I need more parts .
Adam : Hey , May .
Hey , dude , what 's up ?
Not much .
What are you reading about ?
Amputation .
- Is that for work ? - Nope .
It 's just for fun .
Listen , May ,
I 'm sorry things didn 't work out between us .
L ... you know . It just didn 't feel right .
It doesn 't feel right , you know ?
I understand now ...
Adam .
I understand .
Friends ?
Okay . All right .
I really have to go .
Later hands .
Right . All right . See you around .
How 's Lupe ?
- In pieces . - Is she sad about something ?
She does get depressed .
- She doesn 't seem happy . - Oh .
Can I ask what you 're doing ?
I want to make
a blouse for you .
Kind of an apology present for the other night and my behavior .
Oh , May , that is so sweet .
Polly , are you back there , sweetie ?
Polly : Back here .
Did you bring my lunch ?
Oh ...
May , I would like you to meet a new friend of mine .
Her name 's Ambrosia .
Nice gams .
Aren 't they ?
Can I get a few more measurements ?
Have you ever thought about having this removed ?
My grandma said it 's imperfections that make you special .
What do you think ?
Freak .
( giggling )
( muttering )
Hello , Polly , this is May . Happy Halloween .
I was thinking about popping by later to bring you your new blouse .
Show you my costume .
Give me a call if that 's cool . Miss you .
Kisses .
Call me , okay ?
If you can 't find a friend ,
make one .
Hello , May .
Hello , Polly .
Slick duds .
Thank you .
I was going to call you tonight , but ...
I 've been so busy .
What are you doing right now ?
Nothing .
I 'm starting to understand what the doctor 's saying
20 % of the time now .
It 's funny because I always thought it was the doctor 's writing
that was supposed to be incomprehensible .
Maybe it 's different with animal doctors .
Ah , that 's better .
( chuckles )
Are you expecting someone ?
Did you forget my blouse ?
No ? !
You 're not sore about me and Ambrosia , are you ?
I 'm not sore .
You understand it 's not serious , right ?
It 's just a piece of ass .
Whoa !
Whoa .
Oh , please don 't hurt me , May .
Pleasey-please .
I trust you .
I know you would never hurt me , May .
Ambrosia : What are you doing here ?
Where 's Polly ?
In the head .
Polly , hurry up in there !
I 've been drinking vodka all night and I have to piss like a racehorse !
( laughs sarcastically )
You have really beautiful legs .
I thought they were gams ?
Gams , stems , wheels , whatever .
Give us a little spin , doll .
Huh ?
Turn around for me .
You are so fucking weird .
I don 't know what Polly sees in you .
Polly doesn 't see anything .
Turn around , Miss Grable .
Okay , doll .
How was that ?
Beautiful .
Sweet costume .
You got any cold ones in there ?
Yes , I do .
What are you doing here ?
Hello . Anyone home ?
I need them , Adam .
Listen , sister , Adam 's taken for the evening .
I like your earrings .
Thanks .
Nice costume .
Thank you . I made it myself .
Just like one of your movies , Adam .
May ...
what are you doing here ?
This is May ?
Do you want to come in for a drink or something ?
Thank you .
( sighs )
You should have called .
Would you have answered ?
If I was home , yes .
Doesn 't matter . I didn 't come here to see you .
Vodka okay ?
Sounds great .
Did something happen ?
Touch me .
Touch my face .
( giggles )
Go on , Adam , touch my face .
- Stop that ! - These hands are mine now , honey .
No , they are mine , quagledoo .
Fuck you . What is that , Russian or something ?
Touch my face .
Yeah , fucking go on , asshole .
Fucking touch away , I don 't give a shit .
Um ...
Okay ,
I 'm pretty drunk
and I 'm feeling queasy and I just wish you would leave .
Fine , you know what , I 'm out of here .
Not you , dumbshit .
Dumbshit ?
I guess that would be me .
You 're not going to touch my face ?
Fine , I 'll touch your face .
( yells )
You 're going to look perfect .
( grunts )
You have all of the parts .
Words can 't describe .
But I don 't have to talk to you , do I ?
I can just ...
feel .
And you 'll feel it right here , too .
( gasping )
Right .
You can 't see me .
Can 't see me .
( sobbing )
( screaming )
See me !
All I want ...
is see me .
What ...
( screaming )
¶ Bring us all the children ¶
¶ Because they are sweet ¶
¶ Toss them up into the air ¶
¶ They come down and swing their feet ¶
¶ Twirling all the while ¶
¶ Tumbling in a pile ¶
¶ They are good ¶
¶ What a treat ¶
¶ Bring us all the children ¶
¶ Just when they are sweet ¶
¶ Wanderlust and packed with pride ¶
¶ When they laugh and go inside ¶
¶ Echoing all the while ¶
¶ Tumbling in a pile ¶
¶ They are good ¶
¶ Good to eat ¶
¶ Bring us all the children ¶
¶ Even when they 're not so sweet ¶
¶ Toss them up into the air ¶
¶ They come down and get a treat ¶
¶ Bringing tea ¶
¶ A good night 's sleep ¶
¶ It goes away . ¶
¶ ... Love you ¶
¶ You were perfect , and you were made to be ¶
¶ That 's all , that 's all we had to do ¶
¶ That 's all , that 's all we had to see ¶
¶ That 's all , that 's all you faked , you weaved ¶
¶ Walls and walls and walls and walls and walls ¶
¶ Things that I see ¶
¶ Don 't know what they mean ¶
¶ But this I threw in ¶
¶ Good to be all caught up ¶
¶ With no place to go ¶
¶ You were carried away with the words ¶
¶ And I couldn 't follow ¶
¶ They were made up , yet used so cautiously ¶
¶ You were perfect in every way ¶
¶ You were made to love me ¶
¶ Well , that 's all , that 's all we had to do ¶
¶ That 's all , that 's all we had to see ¶
¶ I saw , I saw you straight through these ¶
¶ Walls and walls and walls and walls and walls ¶
¶ Things that I see ¶
¶ Don 't know what they mean ¶
¶ But this I threw in ¶
¶ Good to be all caught up ¶
¶ With no place to go ¶
¶ And the only thing that I know ¶
¶ I was made to love you ¶
¶ The things that I see ¶
¶ Don 't know what they mean ¶
¶ But this I threw in ¶
¶ Good to be all dolled up ¶
¶ The things that we see ¶
¶ You never come clean ¶
¶ But you know what we mean ¶
¶ Good to be broken ¶
¶ Good to be . ¶